bign.com 2017-06-06

# Home

Our Commitment to Privacy

This privacy policy was last updated on February 17th, 2016. Please read carefully. 

Thank you for visiting Team National (the "Site"). Your privacy is very important to us at Team National, and we are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. It is our policy to keep your personal information confidential. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Please take a moment to read the following Policy to learn how we handle your personal information. 

This Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information. 

Team National does not collect Personal Information about individuals who visit our site except when the information is specifically provided on a voluntary basis. 

Information We Collect 

The information we receive depends on what you do when you visit our site. Team National will not collect or retain any information about you personally (that is, your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) unless you choose to provide it to us. If you visit our site to read or download information, we collect and store only the following information: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access our site and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. 

We may collect Personal Information (including name, address, telephone number, email address and, when necessary, credit card information) when you: 

  * Become a Team National Member
  * Place an order from our Web site
  * Return an item or make an exchange
  * Inquire about our products and services
  * Communicate with customer service
  * Place an order through one of our third-party sellers

In addition, you may voluntarily provide Personal Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone number) to be forwarded to a Team National IMD for the purpose of contacting you with details regarding the Team National opportunity, including contact by email. In this case, we will keep a record of the contact, including the Personal Information, in your Team National file. We use this information to provide better service in the event that you contact us again. 

Team National IMD

When you decide to become an authorized Team National IMD, or when you register to shop online as a customer, we will collect Personal Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone number). This Personal Information is securely stored in your Team National contact file. You will be assigned an identification number and you will select a password which will be necessary to gain entrance to the website and to access your Personal Information. 

You expressly consent to our communicating with you about Team National using the information you provided to us. You also attest that you have the legal authority over any telephone number you provide to us and can provide us with the authorization to contact you. This means we may contact you, in person or by recorded message, by e-mail, telephone and/or mobile telephone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message, or any other means of communication that your wireless or other telecommunications device may be capable of receiving. 

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit the Site (e.g., your IP address, browser type, domain name, etc.). This information is collected and analyzed in the aggregate in order to improve the function and content of the Site. 

Use of Information

Personal Information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the website user at the time of collection. The user will have the opportunity to indicate whether he or she would like to "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from Team National and/or any third parties. Further, notwithstanding any "opt out" of promotional information by the user, Team National reserves the right to contact a customer or IMD regarding account status, changes to the IMD Agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected. 

We use the information that is collected about you for a variety of purposes, such as confirming and fulfilling orders, referrals to service partners, adding you to our e-mail subscription list, providing your name to a Team National IMD in connection with potential interest in Team National products or the business opportunity. We also use the information in analyzing trends and statistics, enhancing the operation of the website. 

From time to time you may voluntarily provide Personal Information to complete questionnaires or to participate in contests, polls or personalized assessments. We use this information to improve our products and services. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information we think would be of particular interest to you concerning things such as new products or website features. But you always have the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited promotional materials from us, and we will make every reasonable effort to honor such requests. 

Your mentoring sales organization acts as a support network, providing advice, assistance and information to assist you in building and maintaining a successful Team National business. Therefore, at Team National’s sole discretion, in the best interest of the organization, Team National may share Personal Information with your upline sales organization. They have agreed that such information is confidential, and not to share your information with any non-affiliated third parties, and are obligated to observe the intent of this Privacy Policy.

We work with affiliated businesses we do not control, such as product and service sellers on our website. We share customer information related to any transactions between you and that third party. 

We may share Personal Information you provide online with other Team National-affiliated entities and/or trusted business partners with whom we collaborate. We may employ third party vendors to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include delivering packages, fulfilling orders, e-mail administrative functions, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These vendors will be under bound by contract to use confidential data only for those purposes for which they are hired. 

Team National may disclose Personal Information to a third party in the event that Team National sells all or part of its assets to such third party or merges with or is acquired by the third party. 

Except as stated above or when necessary to share your information with Team National agents or business partners for the purposes of performing services for Team National, your personal information (name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or other information) will not be provided to any third party without your prior consent. We have restricted our agents and business partners from using your personal information in any way other than to provide the services contracted for by Team National. 

We may disclose the information that we collect about you when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities that may be causing injury to you, to us or to others. At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information, and we may also disclose information when we believe the law requires it. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest. 

Users may always "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time. Also, upon request, Team National will take reasonable efforts to delete a user's personal information from its database. It may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions. 

If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States and provide Team National with personal information, please note that your personal information will be transferred, stored and processed within the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By doing business or interacting with Team National, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to facilities located in the United States and other facility locations selected by Team National and to the application of United States law regarding the collection, transfer and maintenance of your personal information.

Cookies

Like many websites, the Team National website uses “cookie” technology. A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a website to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you, except perhaps your first name so we can welcome you on your next visit. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better. 

Data Security

It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant complete security. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection of data. We limit the information we provide to outside companies with whom we contract to only what they need to carry out their responsibilities. When you make a purchase on our Web site, your transactional information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format. 

Every user that has an account on the Website is responsible for (i) keeping his or her account password confidential and secured, (ii) avoiding unauthorized access to his or her computer; and (iii) keeping the e-mail address associated with that account current (you acknowledge that it is important to keep the e-mail address associated with that account current because although you may be able to log into your Team National account using an old e-mail address, you will not receive messages from Team National about your orders and inquiries or other matters). 

You shall be responsible for protecting the confidentiality of your password(s). You acknowledge that, although the Internet is often a secure environment, sometimes there are interruptions in service or events that are beyond our control, and Team National shall not be responsible for any data lost while transmitting or receiving information on the Internet. 

Third Party Websites

The Site may provide hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or to other web sites not controlled by Team National. These hyperlinked web sites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. Team National is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these web sites or links, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure. 

Protection of Children's Privacy 

The Site is a general audience web site that is not specifically designed or targeted at children. If you are under 18, you may use the Site only with involvement of a parent or guardian. We abide by the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and other relevant laws. We do not knowingly collect, use or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If, however, we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a child under the age of 13 has been collected at the Site, we will delete such information from our records. 

Special note for residents of California. 

Your California Privacy Rights. 

Under California Civil Code § 1798.83, we are required to disclose to consumers the following information upon written request: (1) the categories of personal information that we have disclosed to third parties within the prior year, if that information was subsequently used for marketing purposes; and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties to whom such the personal information was disclosed. We hereby disclose that we have not disclosed any such personal information regarding any California resident during the one-year period prior to the effective date of this Privacy and Information Security Policy. California residents seeking additional information on this requirement or our privacy practices in general may write to Customer Service customerservice@bign.com with the headline “PRIVACY REQUEST” in the message line. They may also send paper mail to: 8210 West State Rd. 84 Davie, Florida 33324, USA. Please write "Attention: PRIVACY" in the address. 

How to Access or Correct Your Information 

If you identify any inaccuracy in your personal information, or you need to make a change or would like to verify such information, please contact us so that we may update our records or you may go online to Team National' web site and update your own information. Team National contact information is set forth below. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to accommodate all such requests. 

Modifications to Policy 

The foregoing policies are effective as of February 17th, 2016. Team National reserves the right to change this policy at any time and will notify users of the existence of a new Privacy Policy via e-mail or by posting the latest version on our Site. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon notice. Use of the Site after notice of changes will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are familiar with the most current version. This statement and the policies outlined here are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

How to Contact Us 

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Policy, please send mail to: 8210 West State Road 84 Davie, Florida 33324, send an email to: Customerservice@bign.com. Or, call 954-584-2151. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.
